{
    "subject": "Paul_Spence",
    "predicate": "actedIn",
    "object": "FUBAR__film_",
    "human_readable": "Paul Spence acted in the film FUBAR.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8162910342216492,
            "question": "In which movie does Paul Spence have a role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7480155229568481,
            "question": "What film did Paul Spence act in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6991553902626038,
            "question": "Who is the actor Paul Spence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6463530659675598,
            "question": "Is Paul Spence known for his work in film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5596033334732056,
            "question": "Are there any other notable actors in the film FUBAR?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4515984356403351,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Paul Spence's acting career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4341101050376892,
            "question": "What is the name of the film FUBAR?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4130339026451111,
            "question": "Is FUBAR a well-known film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31306010484695435,
            "question": "What genre is the film FUBAR?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.312542200088501,
            "question": "When was the film FUBAR released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Spence acted in the film FUBAR.",
            "html": "yago_10055_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film FUBAR?",
            "html": "yago_10055_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is FUBAR a well-known film?",
            "html": "yago_10055_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the film FUBAR?",
            "html": "yago_10055_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10055_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10055_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10055_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10055_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10055_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10055_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10055_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10055_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10055_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10055_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references that Paul Spence acted in the film \"FUBAR,\" including details about his role as Dean Murdoch in the 2002 mockumentary film \"FUBAR: The Movie\" and its sequel."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}